ANDREW FISH

Eugene, OR

503-780-1548 | aofish815@gmail.com

LinkedIn: shorturl.at/doDNW | Github: shorturl.at/doDNW | Github: shorturl.at/fP018 | Portfolio: https://superfishal.github.io/fish-portfolio

Summary

Full-stack web developer with a web development certificate from University of Oregon. Extensive background in event production and service industry management provide strong teamwork and communication skills. Ability to design, build and implement project ideas from inception to deployment. Passionate about user experience, accessibility, security, and Web3. Demonstrates leadership, empathy, critical thinking, and adaptability.

Skills

Frontend: HTML5, CSS3, React.js, jQuery, Bootstrap, Tailwind, Handlebars, Figma **Backend:** Node.js, Express.js, MySQL, MongoDB, ORM's, GraphQL, REST API's, Apollo **Development:** Python, JavaScript, Git, Heroku, PWA's, OOP, Agile, Data Structures, Testing

Projects

The Alpha | MERN, Javascript, GraphQL, Apollo, Heroku, Queries, TypeDefs/Mutations/Resolvers *Repository: shorturl.at/mgtxz* | *Deployed: shorturl.at/hklx3*

A scraper for NFT data launching on Magic Eden Marketplace

- Extracts and displays important NFT data on an easy to read card which logged in users can save and delete from their dashboard.
- Demonstrated understanding of API calls, user web tokens and encryption, how to query and structure typeDefs/resolvers/mutations in GraphQL, and connection to the front-end.

PokeBuilder V2 | HTML, Tailwind, Sequelize, Node.js, Handlebars

Repository: shorturl.at/bKT19 | Deployed: shorturl.at/bKT19 | Deployed: shorturl.at/bKT19 | Deployed: shorturl.at/HJLV3

Full-stack application to search through Pokemon monsters by name or number

- User log in capability allows them to save Pokemon to their Pokebelt and view on their profile.
- Styled and designed layout using Tailwind CSS and Handlebars, structured User and Pokemon data for SQL, implemented a RESTful API and CRUD operations.

Deep Thoughts | MERN, GraphQL, Apollo, Faker, Mongoose, JWT, Heroku Repository: <u>shorturl.at/kryKL</u> | Deployed: <u>shorturl.at/hjk24</u>

Single page MERN social-media application for posting thoughts, reactions, and adding friends

- Built API endpoints, queries and mutations to fetch and modify server-side data with GraphQL.
- Implemented authentication functionality using JSON web tokens which updates user-contextualized data on the page.

Tech Blog | Node, Express, Handlebars, HTML, CSS, Javascript, SQL, Sequelize *Repository:* <u>shorturl.at/cINQV</u> | Deployed: <u>shorturl.at/wy045</u>

A CMS- style blog site for tech news and culture, using MVC structure and RESTful API.

Users can sign-up/login to create posts, make comments, and upvote others.

Certain features are not available or pages redirect unless a user is logged in.

Education

Full-Stack Web Developer Certificate University of Oregon (Remote)July 2022UX/UI Foundations DesignLabs (Remote)September 2020EMT Certification Lane Community College - Eugene, ORMay 2018

Experience

Instructional Specialist edX Education

2022-Present

Remote

Support for students and instructors throughout online web development courses

 Responsible for grading, instructing, taking attendance and helping students with course work.

Owner / Bookkeeper Proper Sound LLC

2012-Present

Portland, OR

A music, art and experience collective focused on producing small to large events with exceptional sound and meticulously curated artists.

• Grew from small, free events into ticketed, profit generating shows - now booking artists across the US.

Manager 2021-2022 Luckey's Club Eugene, OR

Responsible for hiring, training and scheduling staff, making orders, working with the public and handling security issues.

- Implemented a training and daily routine manual for current and future employees.
- Upgraded security and customer experience, handled music bookings and navigated COVID mandates to comply with state regulations.

Bartender / Server Viking Braggot Company

2018-2022

Eugene, OR

Helped with construction and opening of a new restaurant for the brewery company, as well as starting their catering service. Responsible for customer satisfaction, money handling and making orders on a daily basis.

 Provided food and full bar catering for the 2022 World Track & Field Championships for Asics.